I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
"Fishing Hole"
Hey! The thing you asked
your friend for came!
Oh that. You brought it for me.
Yeah...
I wanted to see the joy in your face.
Hmm...
This is great.
You're Maho-chan, right?
Huh?
And you were...Izumi-chan?
And it says, "I love New York."
And I got to touch him
when he was running away.
Huh? You touched him?
Neat!
I wanted to talk to you.
Do you have some time now?
Nope.
Oh...
Hmm...Ten minutes is all I need.
Tea? My treat.
I don't know what happened
between you and Maho.
And I don't care.
But...
Hey Koyuki...
The stronger a person looks,
the weaker he is.
Maho looks strong,
but at home, she cries all the time.
Anyway, I have no right to lecture you.
Go!
So what...how do you feel
about my kid sister?
Huh?
Where's Koyuki?
Huh? He went to look for Maho.
Huh?
Maho went to return a video
and hasn't returned for three hours.
Maho?
Don't tell me he's gonna miss
this important meeting for a date!
-Huh? Date?
-That Koyuki!
Here...I brought something.
Thanks.
"Neighborhood Watch-
Work together to prevent crime"
"Liquor, Cigarettes"
"Exciting Town"
Uh?
Huh?
See you, Koyuki.
Huh? Izumi-chan...
Good-bye, Koyuki.
I don't understand Japanese thinking.
Huh?
She hunted me down just to tell me...
that there's nothing between you and her.
At first I thought,
"What the hell do you want?"
After talking to her...
man, she's really nice.
But she seems more like your older sister.
Want to go eat a burger?
Err...no. Ryusuke was worried.
No shit?
But he never acts like a big brother...
Not that article again?
Why're you so stuck on it?
At one time, Eddy and Erica used to date.
We had gone to the
Appollon Theater Amateur Night
and saw Erica before she debuted.
Her powerful singing voice blew me away.
That was the one and only time
we ever waited for someone backstage.
But Eddy and Erica couldn't
get past their problems.
Their relationship didn't last long.
To think that someone
who had such strong vibes
would commit suicide like that...
I just can't believe it.
Hmm...
You think it was murder?
Even the FBI is suspicious.
And the one who benefited most
from Erica's death...
Hmm...
The rapper boyfriend...Malcolm.
Yes. Thank you.
Man, it's totally over.
Hey, are you serious?!
Then that offer from major label...
Just means life ain't so easy.
Wait! I know! Your letters
made the record company mad!
Huh?
Well look...During Dying Breed's
live performance, everything seemed fine!
Well probably...Ran's power
is greater than we thought.
Him?
I get it. So that's how it is.
On top of losing the debut
for Belle Ame, he became a back-up.
He must be mad as hell.
We got ourselves some enemy.
Nah...We just didn't have it.
Excuse me for having
a bad English accent!!
You just don't progress!
And you have a habit of mouthing off!
-I think adding so many
notes about pronunciation...
-Don't lecture me!
Hey Ryusuke...We've been practicing
so much, our motivation is down.
When are we going to record?
-Huh? Record?!
We have to record the ultimate album,
one the industry won't be able to ignore.
If we sit on our asses,
we'll never reach our dream!
What?
An all-night practice at
the studio again on Saturday night?!
-Uh-huh.
You guys are in such a rush.
Think so? It's been the norm lately.
-Right?
-Yeah.
Hmm...You're really working hard, huh?
Huh?
But hey, when you're famous,
I want your autographs.
"Really working hard" huh?
Isn't that him?
Yeah! He was great
at the Culture Festival.
I heard he performs at various live houses.
Huh?
Hey Tanaka!
Come to my office.
"Teachers' Office"
Huh!? That much?
Is it a shock?
But that's the reality for you right now.
Oh...
Tachi High is impossible.
Toyonaga West is also a far reach.
Err...I see.
I'll get right to the point.
You need to change your focus.
You were once in the high middle ranking.
Recently, you've plunged.
Tanaka, it's fine to enjoy your youth.
But the rest of your life is on the line.
Yukio! It's late! Turn down the volume.
All right.
Koyuki-kun! Just like this-108 laps!
It's impossible.
I gave up in four.
No!
Koyuki-kun! You must do your best,
or your dreams will never come true!
I know.
Just like when I made it
on the Olympic team...
when I declared my love
to that pretty bar hostess...
I put my mind to it!
And...your dream came true?
Well...The past is the past
and the present is the present.
Huh?
My dream came true splendidly.
I'm...going home.
So warm!
Cripes! Ryusuke is such a perfectionist!
He's gonna die all alone
when he's old and gray.
Huh?
The hospital...
Hey!
He can't handle an all-nighter.
You'll die, for real!
No...
It's an important time right now.
I can't let the band down.
-Hmm...
All right, once more.
Hey! What're you doing, Koyuki?
There's been no improvement 'cuz of you!
I-I'm sorry.
Hey, hey!
Look, let's take a break.
Uh-uh...Saku, take it from the top.
One, two!
Where is this?
Where...
Oh. Made a big mess.
Too sad.
I'll help.
I'm cleaning up the mess
your concert had made.
When I woke up, my fever, which had
been as high as 103, had gone down.
And Beck's first album was completed
around the middle of winter break.
Uh! Typhoon! Typhoon 24! 24-7, non-stop!
We're gonna rush at you!
Gonna send you flyin'!
Lift up your heavy ass, now
If you take off that stiff head
You'll feel totally loose...
Isn't it great?
Yeah.
And I thought...
What will I be doing with my life?
Koyuki?
Something up?
Nah...Nothing.
But Saku, have you been studying?
Not at all.
You really haven't been studying?
Yup...I really, really
haven't been studying.
Everything began with this one CD.
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
It's almost over!
Let's run towards the sun!
It's blinding!
I wanna be Alain Delon!